Mike Wallace Papers
Mike Wallace Papers
- Interview audiorecordings
  - Dr. Fredric Wertham, wallace_m_048; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:53 (Oversize 2)
  - Phillip Van Rensselaer, wallace_m_049; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 23:47 (Oversize 2)
  - Philip Roth, wallace_m_050; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:46 (Oversize 2)
  - Mae Murray, wallace_m_051; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:18 (Oversize 2)
  - Amy Vanderbilt, wallace_m_052; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:16 (Oversize 2)
  - Anne Bancroft, wallace_m_053; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:15 (Oversize 2)
  - Maureen Stapleton, wallace_m_054; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 23:50 (Oversize 2)
  - Cyrus Eaton, wallace_m_055; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:48 (Oversize 2)
  - Harry Ashmore, wallace_m_056; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:51 (Oversize 2)
  - Paul Whiteman, wallace_m_057; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:19 (Oversize 2)
  - Rube Goldberg, wallace_m_058; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:17 (Oversize 2)
  - Olgivanna Wright, widow of Frank Lloyd Wright., wallace_m_059; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:17 (Oversize 2)
  - Gardner McKay, wallace_m_060; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:20 (Oversize 2)
  - Harry Belafonte, wallace_m_061; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 23:45 (Oversize 2)
  - James Wechsler, wallace_m_062; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:23 (Oversize 2)
  - Joe Louis, wallace_m_063; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:45 (Oversize 2)
  - Faye Emerson, wallace_m_064; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:44 (Oversize 2)
  - Bobby Darin, wallace_m_065; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:44 (Oversize 2)
  - Abba Eban, on location in Israel., wallace_m_066; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:20 (Oversize 2)
  - Moshe Dayan on location in Israel, wallace_m_067; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:45 (Oversize 2)
  - Golda Meir, wallace_m_068; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:20 (Oversize 2)
  - Otto Preminger on location in Israel., wallace_m_069; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:25 (Oversize 2)
  - Paul Newman on location in Israel., wallace_m_070; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:16 (Oversize 2)
  - Thomas F. Lanphier, Jr., wallace_m_071; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:34 (Oversize 2)
  - Sal Mineo on location in Israel, wallace_m_072; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:23 (Oversize 2)
  - William L. Laurence, Science Editor for The New York Times., wallace_m_073; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:22 (Oversize 3)
  - Lee J. Cobb on location in Israel, wallace_m_074; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:21 (Oversize 3)
  - Emmet J. Hughes, chief foreign correspondent for Time and Life magazines., 1959; wallace_m_075; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:11 (Oversize 3)
  - Dr. Albert Ellis on “Morality of Sex, Love and Marriage”, wallace_m_076; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:25 (Oversize 3)
  - Ben Hecht, wallace_m_077; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:28 (Oversize 3)
  - Benjamin Cohen, wallace_m_078; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:46 (Oversize 3)
  - Fred Demara [MISSING Feb 2013], wallace_m_079
  - Mrs. Theodore Roosevelt, Jr. (Eleanor Butler Alexander-Roosevelt), wallace_m_080; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:12 (Oversize 3)
  - June Havoc, wallace_m_081; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:19 (Oversize 3)
  - Sheilah Graham, wallace_m_082; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:53 (Oversize 3)
  - Sammy Davis, Jr., wallace_m_083; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:16 (Oversize 3)
  - Ayn Rand, wallace_m_084; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:47 (Oversize 3)
  - Zsa Zsa Gabor, 1959; wallace_m_085; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:39 (Oversize 3)
  - William F. Buckley, Jr. (Part 1), wallace_m_086; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:15 (Oversize 3)
  - Gerry Mulligan, wallace_m_087; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:51 (Oversize 3)
  - Moss Hart, wallace_m_088; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:43 (Oversize 3)
  - Tommy Leonetti, wallace_m_089; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:41 (Oversize 3)
  - Denise Darcel, wallace_m_090; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:20 (Oversize 3)
  - Norman Mailer, wallace_m_091; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:12 (Oversize 3)
  - George Jessel [MISSING, March 2018], wallace_m_092; reel tape, 1/4"; running time 28:30 (Oversize 3)
  - Eddie Bracken, wallace_m_093; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:15 (Oversize 3)
  - V. K. Krishna Menon, wallace_m_094; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:47 (Oversize 3)
  - Shelley Berman, wallace_m_095; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:45 (Oversize 3)
  - Inger Stevens, wallace_m_096; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:52 (Oversize 3)
  - Melvyn Douglas, 1960; wallace_m_097; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:15 (Oversize 3)
  - Ted Atkinson, wallace_m_098; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:16 (Oversize 3)
  - Sir Cedric Hardwicke, wallace_m_099; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:13 (Oversize 3)
  - Clyde Beatty; circus lions., wallace_m_100; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:11 (Oversize 3)
  - Carol Burnett; slug inserted at 14:39:317 by ?, wallace_m_101; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:39 (Oversize 3)
  - Sam Dash on wiretapping, invasion of privacy, wallace_m_102; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:16 (Oversize 3)
  - Meyer Levin, Jewish activist and author, wallace_m_103; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:24 (Oversize 3)
  - Dana Andrews, wallace_m_104; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:53 (Oversize 3)
  - Orson Bean [MISSING Feb 2013], wallace_m_105
  - Ramon Novarro, silent film actor, wallace_m_106; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:54 (Oversize 3)
  - Leo Rosten, wallace_m_107; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:13 (Oversize 3)
  - Raoul Levy, wallace_m_108; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26;19 (Oversize 3)
  - David Susskind (part 1), wallace_m_109; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:10 (Oversize 4)
  - David Susskind (part 2) [MISSING Feb 2013], wallace_m_110
  - Jersey Joe Walcott, boxer, wallace_m_111; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:14 (Oversize 4)
  - Peter Ustinov, wallace_m_112; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:12 (Oversize 4)
  - James B. Carey, wallace_m_113; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:12 (Oversize 4)
  - Maurice Evans, wallace_m_114; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:43 (Oversize 4)
  - Jinx Falkenberg, wallace_m_115; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:10 (Oversize 4)
  - Joseph Pasternak, wallace_m_116; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:44 (Oversize 4)
  - Carl Sandburg (parts 1 & 2), wallace_m_117; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Ina Balin, actress, and Hugh Downs, wallace_m_118; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - David Susskind - MISSING, wallace_m_119; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - David Susskind and Christina Crawford, wallace_m_120; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Mike Quill and Father Dom Placide Pernot, wallace_m_121; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Malcolm Muggeridge (Part 1 & 2), wallace_m_122; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Quentin Reynolds (part 2) and Fabian, wallace_m_123; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - James Michener and Quentin Reynolds (part 1), wallace_m_124; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Joseph Fletcher and William Michelfelder (Part 1), wallace_m_125; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - William Michelfelder (Part 2) and Nick Kenny, wallace_m_126; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Walter Reuther (Parts 1 & 2), wallace_m_127; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Ilka Chase and Steve Allen, wallace_m_128; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Steve Allen (Part 2) and Myrna Loy, wallace_m_129; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Max Lerner and Robert St. John, wallace_m_130; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Bess Myerson and Col. Gregory (Pappy) Boyington, wallace_m_131; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - Phyllis Diller and Dr. Charles Shulman (Rabbi), wallace_m_132; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:09 (Oversize 4)
  - Robert St. John II, wallace_m_133; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16;23 (Oversize 4)
  - Jack Lemmon and Marya Mannes, wallace_m_134; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:26 (Oversize 4)
  - Harry Wismer, wallace_m_135a; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:08 (Oversize 4)
  - Morarji Desai, wallace_m_135b; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 17:28 (Oversize 4)
  - Dr. Fredric Wertham and Louis Lomax, wallace_m_136; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:38 (Oversize 4)
  - William Bendix and Gael Greene, wallace_m_137; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 17:03 (Oversize 4)
  - Gael Greene, wallace_m_137a; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 4)
  - David Merrick, 1/11/1961; wallace_m_138; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:21 (Oversize 4)
  - Mel Brooks, wallace_m_139; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:50 (Oversize 4)
  - Otto Preminger, 1/12/1961; wallace_m_140; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:29 (Oversize 4)
  - Elizabeth Seal, take 1, 1/12/1961; wallace_m_141; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 22:06 (Oversize 4)
  - Gus Hall, take 1, 1/5/1961; wallace_m_142; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:30 (Oversize 4)
  - Jim Landis; Take 2, 1/11/1961; wallace_m_143; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 29:31 (Oversize 4)
  - Lilo, wallace_m_144; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:06 (Oversize 4)
  - Sal Mineo, wallace_m_145; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:53 (Oversize 5)
  - Willis Stone, wallace_m_146; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:45 (Oversize 5)
  - Piper Laurie, wallace_m_147; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:41 (Oversize 5)
  - David Susskind (part 2), wallace_m_148; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:41 (Oversize 5)
  - Menachem Begin and a Promotional O.T.A., wallace_m_149; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 14:49 (Oversize 5)
  - Gloria DeHaven, wallace_m_150; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:38 (Oversize 5)
  - Dr. Gregory Pincus, birth control pill inventor, wallace_m_151; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:44 (Oversize 5)
  - Natasha Lytess, wallace_m_152; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:42 (Oversize 5)
  - Dr. Linus Pauling, wallace_m_153; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:56 (Oversize 5)
  - Connie Francis; including commercials, wallace_m_154; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:24 (Oversize 5)
  - Mary Margaret McBride and Joseph Granville, wallace_m_155; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:06 (Oversize 5)
  - Sammy Davis Jr., wallace_m_156; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:36 (Oversize 5)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Sammy Davis Jr.; including commercials, wallace_m_157; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:01 (Oversize 5)
  - Captain James Calvert, wallace_m_158; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:57 (Oversize 5)
  - William L. Shirer, author of The Rise And Fall Of The Third Reich, wallace_m_159; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:58 (Oversize 5)
  - John Bonomi, wallace_m_160a; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:06 (Oversize 5)
  - Cleveland Amory, wallace_m_160b; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:29 (Oversize 5)
  - Phil Ford & Mimi Hines, wallace_m_161a; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:11 (Oversize 5)
  - Henry Rosenfeld, wallace_m_161b; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:23 (Oversize 5)
  - Frank Meyer, wallace_m_162; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:52 (Oversize 5)
  - Buddy Rich, wallace_m_163; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:15 (Oversize 5)
  - Duchess of Bedford, wallace_m_164; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:42 (Oversize 5)
  - Renee Taylor; take 1; studio banter and cues, slate, wallace_m_165; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:56 (Oversize 5)
  - Louis Wyman, wallace_m_166; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 17:44 (Oversize 5)
  - Pamela Mason (Mrs.James Mason); with commercials, wallace_m_167; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:23 (Oversize 5)
  - Anne Meacham; poor recording, wallace_m_168; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:02 (Oversize 5)
  - Paul Anka; with commercials, wallace_m_169; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:50 (Oversize 5)
  - William F. Buckley Jr.; with commercials, wallace_m_170; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:15 (Oversize 5)
  - Mike Nichols; with commercials, wallace_m_171; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:24 (Oversize 5)
  - Oleg Cassini, wallace_m_172; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:49 (Oversize 5)
  - Eve Merriam; with commercials, wallace_m_173; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:17 (Oversize 5)
  - Marcel Duchamp; with commercials, wallace_m_174; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:38 (Oversize 5)
  - John Cassevetes; Dialing the News (fragment), wallace_m_175; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:24 (Oversize 5)
  - Norman Mailer, 11/21/1960; wallace_m_177; interview was recorded the day before Mr. Mailer was arrested for the stabbing of Mrs. Adele Mailer on 11/22/1960. The NYPD was allowed to view the tape before broadcast.; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:22 (Oversize 5)
  - Maurice Zolotow; with commercials, wallace_m_178; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:51 (Oversize 5)
  - Burr Tillstrom, Kukla and Ollie the Dragon about their show at the Kuklapolitan Room, NYC among other subjects; Dialing the News (fragment); with commercials, wallace_m_179; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time "19:51" (Oversize 5)
  - Andre Maurois and Christina Crawford; includes news fragment, commercials, wallace_m_180; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:10 (Oversize 5)
  - Leo Koch; includies a "Dialing the News" fragment, wallace_m_181; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:39 (Oversize 6)
  - John Crosby; with commercials, wallace_m_182; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 17:34 (Oversize 6)
  - Barbara Baxley and the news; with commercials, wallace_m_183; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:27 (Oversize 6)
  - Dr. Willard Uphous; with commercials, wallace_m_184; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 23:08 (Oversize 6)
  - Connee Boswell, wallace_m_185; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:46 (Oversize 6)
  - Frank Conniff, Moss Hart (fragment) and Christine Jorgensen (fragment), wallace_m_186; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 16:14 (Oversize 6)
  - Victor Riesel; with commercials, wallace_m_187; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:42 (Oversize 6)
  - Zachary Scott, wallace_m_188; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 27:05 (Oversize 6)
  - Rod Steiger, wallace_m_189; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 22:15 (Oversize 6)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. (Part 1), wallace_m_190; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 6)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. (Part 2), wallace_m_191; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 6)
  - Earl Bucholz, tennis player; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_192; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:42 (Oversize 6)
  - Robert Gray; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_193; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 17:13 (Oversize 6)
  - Nancy Walker; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_194; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 17:41 (Oversize 6)
  - Eli Wallach; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_195; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:49 (Oversize 6)
  - Henny Youngman; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_196; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:47 (Oversize 6)
  - Diahann Carroll; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_197; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:43 (Oversize 6)
  - Merriam Smith; with studio banter and cues; no commercials; no footnote or close @ end, wallace_m_198; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 24:02 (Oversize 6)
  - Dr. Leo Sziliard; with studio banter and cues; no commercials; unimportant fluffs, false starts,and tech problems edited from transfer, wallace_m_199; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 27:04 (Oversize 6)
  - Gayelord Hauser; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_200; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:07 (Oversize 6)
  - Isaac Stern; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, 01/11/1961; wallace_m_201; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 29:31 (Oversize 6)
  - Mel Torme; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, 02/17/1961; wallace_m_202; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:57 (Oversize 6)
  - Henry "Champ" Segal; with studio banter and cues, 02/15/1961; wallace_m_203; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:54 (Oversize 6)
  - Bishop James Pike; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_204; has date of Feb 21, no year; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 29:21 (Oversize 6)
  - Vincent Tracy; with studio banter and cues; no commercials; inconsequential fluffs and gaffes edited, 1/5/1961; wallace_m_205; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 19:43 (Oversize 6)
  - China Machado; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, 3/2/1961; wallace_m_206; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 27:21 (Oversize 6)
  - Betty Comden and Adolph Green; with studio banter and cues; no commercials, 2/17/1961; wallace_m_207; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:20 (Oversize 6)
  - Elsa Lanchester; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_208; has date of Feb 23, no year; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:03 (Oversize 6)
  - Eddie Albert; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_209; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:15 (Oversize 6)
  - Carol Channing; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_210; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 23:17 (Oversize 6)
  - Dr. Richard Hoffman, wallace_m_211; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 6)
  - Dr. Lewis L Robbins; studio banter and cues; no commercials, 02/10/1961; wallace_m_212; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:04 (Oversize 6)
  - Ben Hecht and Dore Schary; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_213; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 22:00 (Oversize 6)
  - Gary Crosby and Dizzy Gillespie; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_214; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:52 (Oversize 6)
  - Bobby Darin and Karl Malden; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_215; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:04 (Oversize 6)
  - Primo Carnera and Betty Furness; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_216; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:43 (Oversize 6)
  - Dick van Dyke; studio banter and cues; no commercials; Pre “Dick Van Dyke Show”, 02/17/1961; wallace_m_218; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:27 (Oversize 7)
  - Joyce McIver; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_219; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:01 (Oversize 7)
  - Frank Gifford, Hal March and Winston Churchill documentary (2 fragments); studio banter and cues, wallace_m_220; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:08 (Oversize 7)
  - Margaret O’Brien, P.D. East and Winston Churchill documentary (fragment); studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_221; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:22 (Oversize 7)
  - Carol Lynley and “Bricktop”; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_222; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:48 (Oversize 7)
  - Orson Bean by Mike Wallace, wallace_m_223; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 26:13 (Oversize 7)
  - Henry Kissinger and Dennis King; studio banter and cues, wallace_m_224; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 18:06 (Oversize 7)
  - Richard Rodgers and Tony Bennett; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_225; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:45 (Oversize 7)
  - Ayn Rand; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_226; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:23 (Oversize 7)
  - Alexander P. de Seversky by Mike Wallace; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_227; reel tape, 7", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:49 (Oversize 7)
  - Janice Rule and Andy Robustelli; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_228; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 20:49 (Oversize 7)
  - Roald Dahl by Mike Wallace, wallace_m_229; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 22:56 (Oversize 7)
  - Eartha Kitt by Mike Wallace; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_230; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 22:19 (Oversize 7)
  - Zsa Zsa Gabor; studio banter and cues; no commercials; first introduction is an out take, wallace_m_231; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 36:00 (Oversize 7)
  - Carmelo Soraci, Anita Loos; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_232; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; running time 20:27 (Oversize 7)
  - Kim Hunter and Ruby Dee, wallace_m_233; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 25:05 (Oversize 7)
  - Elsa Maxwell; Studio banter and cues; no commercials; 1 out take, wallace_m_234; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; running time 21:16 (Oversize 7)
  - Roddy MacDowall and Hazel Scott; studio banter with cues; no commercials, wallace_m_235; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 42:45 (Oversize 7)
  - Cyril Richard and Luther Hodges; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_236; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 21:14 (Oversize 7)
  - Hazel Scott and Dick Gregory; studio banter and cues; no commercials, wallace_m_237; reel tape, 1/4", 7 1/2 ips; running time 41:58 (Oversize 7)
  - June Havoc, Cyrus Eaton, Ayn Rand and Sammy Davis Jr., 03/9/1959 to 3/13/1959; wallace_m_239; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; four separate interviews, total running time 104:29 (Oversize 7)
  - Hubert Humphrey, Hans Conreid, Ted Atkinson, Clayton Pruell, Martin Block and Orson Bean, wallace_m_240; dates are given as 3/17, 3/18, 3/19, 3/20, 3/23, 3/24 with no year; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 154:00 (Oversize 7)
  - Tommy Leonetti, Zsa Zsa Gabor, William Buckley Jr., Jayne Meadows, Ben Hecht, and Dr. Albert Ellis, wallace_m_241; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 175:51 (Oversize 7)
  - Sally Belfrage, Gerald [Gerold?] Frank, Eugene Kinkead, Rube Goldberg, Gov. G. Mennen Williams, and Clyde Beatty, wallace_m_242; same as wallace_m_100; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 171:37 (Oversize 7)
  - Jack Douglas, Marie McDonald, Dana Andrews, Ethel Waters, Capt. William Bradley, and Mike Quill, wallace_m_243; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 173:28 (Oversize 7)
  - Col. Serge Obolensky, Abbe Lane, Xavier Cugat, Pancho Gonzalez, Myoshi Umeki and Christine Jorgensen, wallace_m_244; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 148:41 (Oversize 7)
  - Sir Cedric Hardwicke, Camilo Weston Leyra, Frankie Laine, Shelley Berman, May Eastman, Hy Gardner, wallace_m_245; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 174:52 (Oversize 7)
  - Sessue Hayakawa, David Susskind, Ephraim London, Lorraine Hansberry and Gore Vidal, wallace_m_246 (Oversize 7)
  - Mr. John, Kyre Petrovskaya, Maureen Stapleton, Tony Galento, Jackie Gerlich, and Andy Griffith, wallace_m_247; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 175:37 (Oversize 7)